<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academic</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Academic</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Academic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>On How Awesome Tom Hardy Is</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publication/conference-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publication/conference-paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-the-authors-of-this-research-believe-that-tom-hardy-is-one-of-the-most-talented-and-charismatic-actors-of-our-time-his-incredible-ability-to-transform-his-deep-understanding-of-human-nature-and-his-unique-screen-charisma-make-him-a-true-benchmark-of-acting-in-this-research-we-will-analyze-key-aspects-of-tom-hardys-work-and-reveal-why-he-deserves-the-title-of-dream-actor&#34;&gt;We, the authors of this research, believe that Tom Hardy is one of the most talented and charismatic actors of our time. His incredible ability to transform, his deep understanding of human nature, and his unique screen charisma make him a true benchmark of acting. In this research, we will analyze key aspects of Tom Hardy&amp;rsquo;s work and reveal why he deserves the title of &amp;ldquo;Dream Actor&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;early-career-and-development&#34;&gt;Early Career and Development&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tom-hardy-was-born-in-1977-in-london-from-an-early-age-he-showed-an-interest-in-acting-and-began-participating-in-theatrical-productions-as-a-teenager-his-first-major-breakthrough-was-his-role-in-the-2001-film-black-hawk-down-where-he-played-a-young-british-soldier-this-role-demonstrated-his-ability-to-deeply-transform-and-drew-attention-to-his-talent&#34;&gt;Tom Hardy was born in 1977 in London. From an early age, he showed an interest in acting and began participating in theatrical productions as a teenager. His first major breakthrough was his role in the 2001 film &amp;ldquo;Black Hawk Down,&amp;rdquo; where he played a young British soldier. This role demonstrated his ability to deeply transform and drew attention to his talent.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;rise-to-the-top&#34;&gt;Rise to the Top&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;after-the-success-of-black-hawk-down-tom-hardys-career-skyrocketed-he-starred-in-such-iconic-films-as-inception-the-dark-knight-rises-the-revenant-and-mad-max-fury-road-in-each-of-these-roles-hardy-demonstrated-his-unique-ability-to-fully-immerse-himself-in-the-image-whether-it-be-a-ruthless-criminal-a-tortured-survivor-or-a-harsh-warrior-his-acting-is-always-distinguished-by-incredible-depth-and-persuasiveness-causing-viewers-to-fully-immerse-themselves-in-what-is-happening-on-the-screen&#34;&gt;After the success of &amp;ldquo;Black Hawk Down,&amp;rdquo; Tom Hardy&amp;rsquo;s career skyrocketed. He starred in such iconic films as &amp;ldquo;Inception,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Dark Knight Rises,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Revenant,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Mad Max: Fury Road.&amp;rdquo; In each of these roles, Hardy demonstrated his unique ability to fully immerse himself in the image, whether it be a ruthless criminal, a tortured survivor, or a harsh warrior. His acting is always distinguished by incredible depth and persuasiveness, causing viewers to fully immerse themselves in what is happening on the screen.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-secret-of-success&#34;&gt;The Secret of Success&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;one-of-the-key-factors-in-tom-hardys-success-is-his-incredible-charisma-and-ability-to-create-memorable-images-he-has-the-ability-to-endow-his-characters-with-unique-personality-traits-be-it-brutality-vulnerability-or-intellectual-sophistication-this-allows-him-to-create-truly-multifaceted-and-realistic-characters-that-remain-in-the-minds-of-viewers-for-a-long-time&#34;&gt;One of the key factors in Tom Hardy&amp;rsquo;s success is his incredible charisma and ability to create memorable images. He has the ability to endow his characters with unique personality traits, be it brutality, vulnerability, or intellectual sophistication. This allows him to create truly multifaceted and realistic characters that remain in the minds of viewers for a long time.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-addition-tom-hardy-carefully-chooses-roles-giving-preference-to-projects-that-allow-him-to-unleash-his-acting-potential-he-is-not-afraid-to-take-on-complex-and-ambiguous-images-which-only-strengthens-his-creative-individuality&#34;&gt;In addition, Tom Hardy carefully chooses roles, giving preference to projects that allow him to unleash his acting potential. He is not afraid to take on complex and ambiguous images, which only strengthens his creative individuality.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-conclusion-we-can-confidently-say-that-tom-hardy-is-one-of-the-most-outstanding-actors-of-his-generation-his-unique-talent-depth-of-transformation-and-screen-charisma-make-him-a-truly-dream-actor-we-hope-that-his-work-will-continue-to-inspire-and-delight-audiences-around-the-world-for-many-years-to-come&#34;&gt;In conclusion, we can confidently say that Tom Hardy is one of the most outstanding actors of his generation. His unique talent, depth of transformation, and screen charisma make him a truly &amp;ldquo;Dream Actor.&amp;rdquo; We hope that his work will continue to inspire and delight audiences around the world for many years to come.&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab Work Discussion on Discord.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/talk/lab-work-discussion-on-discord./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/talk/lab-work-discussion-on-discord./</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;grab-your-cookies-and-hot-tea-3&#34;&gt;Grab your cookies and hot tea :3&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update (May 20-26)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypostmay-1-%D1%8F-%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BF%D0%B8%D1%8F/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypostmay-1-%D1%8F-%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BF%D0%B8%D1%8F/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;academics&#34;&gt;Academics:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;exam-season-is-approaching-lots-of-tests-to-prepare-for-im-proud-of-myself-for-completing-a-challenging-extra-assignment-in-math-logic-as-a-result-ill-be-able-to-finish-the-semester-without-exams&#34;&gt;Exam season is approaching! Lots of tests to prepare for. I&amp;rsquo;m proud of myself for completing a challenging extra assignment in math logic. As a result, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to finish the semester without exams.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-also-tried-writing-a-program-for-programming-technology-that-included-a-database-which-was-a-very-interesting-experience&#34;&gt;I also tried writing a program for Programming Technology that included a database, which was a very interesting experience.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;free-time&#34;&gt;Free Time:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;surprisingly-despite-being-busy-i-managed-to-watch-a-couple-of-great-movies--good-old-classics-the-intouchables-and-the-gentlemen-left-a-great-impression-im-happy-with-my-choices&#34;&gt;Surprisingly, despite being busy, I managed to watch a couple of great movies – good old classics. &amp;ldquo;The Intouchables&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Gentlemen&amp;rdquo; left a great impression. I&amp;rsquo;m happy with my choices!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;last-week-moscow-had-museum-week-and-i-was-able-to-visit-the-museum-of-cosmonautics-at-vdnkh&#34;&gt;Last week, Moscow had &amp;ldquo;Museum Week,&amp;rdquo; and I was able to visit the Museum of Cosmonautics at VDNKh.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;overall-it-was-an-interesting-albeit-hectic-week&#34;&gt;Overall, it was an interesting, albeit hectic week.&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update (May 6-12)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypostmay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypostmay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;not-a-super-productive-week-as-it-was-a-holiday-week-and-i-took-some-time-to-relax&#34;&gt;Not a super productive week, as it was a holiday week and I took some time to relax.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;on-the-bright-side-i-rewatched-a-few-movies-that-i-didnt-understand-before-its-nice-to-finally-get-them&#34;&gt;On the bright side, I rewatched a few movies that I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand before. It&amp;rsquo;s nice to finally get them!&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BookSharing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/example/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Report Formatting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchooseapril2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchooseapril2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;markdown-report-formatting-simple-and-elegant&#34;&gt;Markdown Report Formatting: Simple and Elegant&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a simple and effective way to format your reports, Markdown might be the perfect solution. Markdown is a lightweight markup language that allows you to quickly create structured documents without the need for complex editors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-markdown&#34;&gt;What is Markdown?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is a plain text formatting language that uses a set of special symbols to format text. It was created to make it easier to write and read documents in a simple text format that can easily be converted to HTML and other formats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;advantages-of-using-markdown-for-reports&#34;&gt;Advantages of Using Markdown for Reports&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplicity&lt;/strong&gt;: Markdown syntax is intuitive and easy to learn. You can start using it almost immediately without having to learn complex tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Readability&lt;/strong&gt;: Documents written in Markdown are easy to read even in their raw form, without needing to be converted to other formats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portability&lt;/strong&gt;: Markdown files are plain text files that can be opened in any text editor on any platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;: Markdown allows you to easily convert documents into various formats such as HTML, PDF or Word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;basic-markdown-formatting-elements&#34;&gt;Basic Markdown Formatting Elements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headings: Use the &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; symbols to create headings of different levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lists: Use &lt;code&gt;-&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;*&lt;/code&gt; for unordered lists and numbers for ordered lists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Text Emphasis: Use &lt;code&gt;*&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;_&lt;/code&gt; for italics and &lt;code&gt;**&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;__&lt;/code&gt; for bold.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Links: Use &lt;code&gt;[link text](URL)&lt;/code&gt; to create links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Images: Use &lt;code&gt;![alt text](image URL)&lt;/code&gt; to insert images.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-start-using-markdown-for-reports&#34;&gt;How to Start Using Markdown for Reports&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose a Markdown-compatible editor. This can be a simple text editor or a specialized application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn the basics of Markdown syntax. It will only take a short amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start writing your report using Markdown formatting elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If necessary, convert your document to the desired format (HTML, PDF, Word) using special tools or online converters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using Markdown for report formatting can significantly simplify your work and save you time. Try this approach and you will appreciate its efficiency and convenience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientific Programming Languages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchoosemay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchoosemay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;scientific-programming-languages&#34;&gt;Scientific Programming Languages&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientific programming languages play a vital role in scientific computing, data analysis, and modeling. They provide researchers and scientists with powerful tools to solve complex problems and conduct experiments. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at some of the most popular scientific programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-python&#34;&gt;1. Python&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Python is one of the most widely used programming languages in the scientific community. It offers the following advantages:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simple and clear syntax&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A large number of scientific libraries, such as NumPy, SciPy, and Pandas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration with other languages, such as C and Fortran&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for data visualization using libraries like Matplotlib and Seaborn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example Python code for calculating the mean of an array:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;import numpy as np&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;data = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]
mean = np.mean(data)
print(f&amp;quot;Mean value: {mean}&amp;quot;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-r&#34;&gt;2. R&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;R is a programming language specifically designed for statistical computing and data analysis. Its main features include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A large number of statistical functions and methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for data visualization using the ggplot2 package&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration with other languages, such as C++ and Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An active community of users and developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example R code for creating a histogram:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;data &amp;lt;- c(1, 2, 2, 3, 3, 3, 4, 4, 5)
hist(data, main = &amp;ldquo;Histogram&amp;rdquo;, xlab = &amp;ldquo;Values&amp;rdquo;, ylab = &amp;ldquo;Frequency&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-matlab&#34;&gt;3. MATLAB&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MATLAB is a proprietary programming language widely used in engineering and scientific applications. Its key features include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A convenient interface for working with matrices and arrays&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A large number of built-in mathematical functions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for data visualization and plotting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration with other languages, such as C and Java&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example MATLAB code for solving a system of linear equations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A = [1 2; 3 4];
b = [5; 11];
x = A \ b;
disp(x);&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientific programming languages provide researchers and scientists with powerful tools for data analysis, modeling, and solving complex problems. Python, R, and MATLAB are some of the most popular languages in this field, each with its own strengths and features. Choosing the right language depends on the specific project requirements and user preferences.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Korea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchoosemay1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchoosemay1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;south-korea-the-land-of-morning-calm&#34;&gt;South Korea: The Land of Morning Calm&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;culture&#34;&gt;Culture&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;South Korea is renowned for its unique and rich culture. The Korean peninsula boasts an ancient history dating back to the 4th millennium BCE. Over the centuries, South Korea has developed distinctive traditions, arts, music, and cuisine. Koreans are proud of their national heritage and actively support its development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;location&#34;&gt;Location&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;South Korea occupies the southern portion of the Korean Peninsula and shares a border with North Korea to the north. The country is bordered by the Sea of Japan to the east, the East China Sea to the south, and the Yellow Sea to the west. Its capital and largest city is Seoul, located in the northwestern part of the country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;history&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Korean peninsula has a long and eventful history. The first state formations on its territory emerged in the 1st century BCE. During the Middle Ages, three major kingdoms existed on the peninsula: Goguryeo, Baekje, and Silla. In 1392, the Joseon dynasty was established, lasting until 1897. In the 20th century, Korea experienced a period of Japanese occupation, and after World War II, it was divided into North and South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;religion&#34;&gt;Religion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main religions in South Korea are Buddhism and Christianity. Buddhism was introduced to Korea from China in the 4th century CE and gained widespread acceptance. Christianity arrived in the late 19th century and is now one of the largest religions in the country. Elements of traditional beliefs, such as Confucianism and Shamanism, also persist in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;language&#34;&gt;Language&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The official language of South Korea is Korean. It belongs to the Altaic language family and has its own unique writing system – the Korean alphabet Hangul. Korean is considered one of the most complex languages in the world, as it features a complex system of politeness and numerous dialects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update (April 22-28)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypost_april2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypost_april2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;achievements&#34;&gt;Achievements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I came in second place in the Analytics Olympiad finals! I also attended the award ceremony. Feeling good about myself!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I built a website for the olympiad finals based on the concept of my product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;academics&#34;&gt;Academics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried to write a program for the Programming Technology lab assignment, incorporating a graphics library. It was an interesting experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;free-time&#34;&gt;Free Time&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week was my birthday! I finally turned 18, yay!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;overall&#34;&gt;Overall&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was an interesting week, but not super productive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Markup Language</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchooseapril/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchooseapril/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;markdown-markup-language&#34;&gt;Markdown Markup Language&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is a simple and easy-to-use markup language that allows you to quickly and easily format text for publication on the internet. It was created in 2004 by John Gruber and Aaron Swartz to simplify the process of writing and reading text in HTML format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;advantages-of-markdown&#34;&gt;Advantages of Markdown&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main advantage of Markdown is its simplicity and readability. Unlike HTML, where tags are used to format text, Markdown uses simple and intuitive symbols. For example, to italicize text, you need to surround it with asterisks (*), and to bold it, you need to use double asterisks (**). This makes text written with Markdown easy to read even in its raw form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another advantage of Markdown is its versatility. Many platforms and services, such as GitHub, Stack Overflow, Reddit and many others, support Markdown. This means you can use the same format to write documentation, articles, comments, and other types of content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;basic-markdown-elements&#34;&gt;Basic Markdown Elements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some basic elements you can use in Markdown:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Headings: Use the # symbol to create headings of different levels (# for H1, ## for H2, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lists: Use - or * symbols to create unordered lists and numbers for ordered lists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Links: Use square brackets for link text and parentheses for URL (e.g., &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Images: Use an exclamation mark, square brackets for alternate text, and parentheses for the image URL (e.g., 















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;image.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Alt Text&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quotes: Use the &amp;gt; symbol to create quote blocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code: Use backticks (`) to highlight inline code and triple backticks (```) for code blocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is a powerful and easy-to-use markup language that can significantly simplify the process of creating content for web publications. Due to its readability and versatility, Markdown has become one of the most popular formats for writing documentation, articles, and other types of content on the internet. By mastering the basics of Markdown, you can quickly and efficiently create high-quality content for your projects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update (April 1-7)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypost_april/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypost_april/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;academics&#34;&gt;Academics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week was all about exams! I finished my math logic and calculus tests.  I also aced another Korean language test, scoring the highest again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-adventures&#34;&gt;New Adventures&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made it to the finals of an analytics olympiad and started working on developing the website I proposed in the semi-finals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;free-time&#34;&gt;Free Time&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to an exhibition dedicated to the phenomenon of &amp;ldquo;manga,&amp;rdquo; but for me, it was specifically about &amp;ldquo;manhwa.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learned that to be a Korean translator, you only need to have a level 3 &amp;ldquo;gyp&amp;rdquo; (Korean language proficiency level). I think I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to confirm my level soon and try my hand at that kind of work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;overall&#34;&gt;Overall&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a pretty productive week, I&amp;rsquo;m happy!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Admission to RUDN</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publication/journal-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publication/journal-article/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;as-a-first-year-student-at-rudn-studying-business-informatics-on-a-paid-basis-im-happy-to-share-my-experience-of-getting-into-this-prestigious-university&#34;&gt;As a first-year student at RUDN, studying &amp;ldquo;Business Informatics&amp;rdquo; on a paid basis, I&amp;rsquo;m happy to share my experience of getting into this prestigious university.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-process-started-long-before-graduation-exams-at-school-i-carefully-studied-information-about-rudn-its-programs-and-requirements-for-applicants-since-i-chose-business-informatics-i-paid-special-attention-to-the-subjects-taken-in-the-unified-state-exam---russian-language-profile-mathematics-and-english&#34;&gt;The process started long before graduation exams at school. I carefully studied information about RUDN, its programs, and requirements for applicants. Since I chose &amp;ldquo;Business Informatics&amp;rdquo;, I paid special attention to the subjects taken in the Unified State Exam - Russian language, profile mathematics and English.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;when-it-was-time-to-submit-documents-i-carefully-filled-out-all-necessary-forms-and-prepared-a-package-of-documents-in-accordance-with-the-requirements-of-the-admissions-committee-this-included-a-certificate-photos-copies-of-my-passport-and-other-identification-documents-as-well-as-documents-confirming-my-paid-education&#34;&gt;When it was time to submit documents, I carefully filled out all necessary forms and prepared a package of documents in accordance with the requirements of the admissions committee. This included a certificate, photos, copies of my passport and other identification documents, as well as documents confirming my paid education.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;then-i-anxiously-awaited-the-results-of-the-entrance-examinations-to-my-joy-my-efforts-paid-off-and-i-successfully-passed-the-competitive-selection-when-i-saw-my-name-on-the-list-of-enrolled-students-i-felt-a-huge-sense-of-pride-and-gratitude-for-the-opportunity-to-become-part-of-the-rudn-student-community&#34;&gt;Then, I anxiously awaited the results of the entrance examinations. To my joy, my efforts paid off, and I successfully passed the competitive selection. When I saw my name on the list of enrolled students, I felt a huge sense of pride and gratitude for the opportunity to become part of the RUDN student community.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;now-as-a-rudn-student-i-am-looking-forward-to-the-start-of-the-academic-process-and-the-opportunity-to-prove-myself-within-the-walls-of-this-wonderful-university-i-am-confident-that-the-knowledge-and-experience-gained-here-will-become-the-foundation-for-my-further-professional-and-personal-development-in-the-field-of-business-informatics&#34;&gt;Now, as a RUDN student, I am looking forward to the start of the academic process and the opportunity to prove myself within the walls of this wonderful university. I am confident that the knowledge and experience gained here will become the foundation for my further professional and personal development in the field of business informatics.&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version Control with Git.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchoose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/postonchoose/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;version-control-with-git&#34;&gt;Version Control with Git&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Git is a distributed version control system that has become an indispensable tool for software developers. It allows you to effectively manage code changes, collaborate with other developers, and track the history of your project. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the key concepts and commands of Git.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-concepts-of-git&#34;&gt;Key Concepts of Git&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repository - This is a storage place for your project, containing all files and change history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commit represents a snapshot of the project&amp;rsquo;s state at a particular point in time. Each commit has a unique identifier and a message describing the changes made.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Branch is an independent line of development in the repository. It allows you to work on new features or fixes without affecting the main branch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merge is the process of combining changes from one branch into another. This allows you to integrate new features or fixes into the main branch of the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-git-commands&#34;&gt;Key Git Commands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git init&lt;/strong&gt;: Initializes a new Git repository in the current directory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git clone&lt;/strong&gt;: Clones an existing repository to your local machine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git add&lt;/strong&gt;: Adds changes to the index for subsequent commit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git commit&lt;/strong&gt;: Creates a new commit with added changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git status&lt;/strong&gt;: Displays the current state of the repository, showing changed, added, and deleted files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git branch&lt;/strong&gt;: Manages branches, allowing you to create, delete, and switch between branches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git merge&lt;/strong&gt;: Merges changes from one branch into the current branch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git pull&lt;/strong&gt;: Downloads changes from the remote repository and merges them into the current branch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;git push&lt;/strong&gt;: Sends local commits to the remote repository.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;benefits-of-using-git&#34;&gt;Benefits of Using Git&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Versioning: Git allows you to save the history of changes, making it easier to track and revert to previous versions of the code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboration: Git simplifies collaboration on a project, allowing multiple developers to work in parallel and merge their changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Branching: Branches in Git provide flexibility and isolation when developing new features or fixing bugs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Distribution: Git is a distributed system, which means that every developer has a full copy of the repository and can work autonomously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Git is a powerful tool that significantly simplifies version control and collaboration on projects. By mastering the key concepts and commands of Git, you can effectively control changes in your code and collaborate with other developers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Update (March 11-17)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/weeklypost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;academics&#34;&gt;Academics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week was more chill and focused on relaxation. I completed my Programming Technology lab assignment. I also aced my Korean language exam, scoring the highest in the group! Feeling proud of myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-adventures&#34;&gt;New Adventures&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried installing and getting familiar with Scilab. It reminded me a lot of Pascal, the language that started my programming journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;free-time&#34;&gt;Free Time&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally finished reading &amp;ldquo;Little Women&amp;rdquo; by Louisa May Alcott. Feeling a bit empty now. The movie with Timothée Chalamet is a complete flop compared to the book :(&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/slides/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/slides/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;create-slides-in-markdown-with-hugo-blox-builder&#34;&gt;Create slides in Markdown with Hugo Blox Builder&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hugoblox.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hugo Blox Builder&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.hugoblox.com/content/slides/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports speaker notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;controls&#34;&gt;Controls&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next: &lt;code&gt;Right Arrow&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous: &lt;code&gt;Left Arrow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start: &lt;code&gt;Home&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish: &lt;code&gt;End&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overview: &lt;code&gt;Esc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaker notes: &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fullscreen: &lt;code&gt;F&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zoom: &lt;code&gt;Alt + Click&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://revealjs.com/pdf-export/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PDF Export&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-highlighting&#34;&gt;Code Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inline code: &lt;code&gt;variable&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Code block:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34; data-lang=&#34;python&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;n&#34;&gt;porridge&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;blueberry&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;n&#34;&gt;porridge&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;==&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;blueberry&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Eating...&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;math&#34;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Block math:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f\left( x \right) = ;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fragments&#34;&gt;Fragments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-fallback&#34; data-lang=&#34;fallback&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt; to play!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  One
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  Three
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt;: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;weight&lt;/code&gt;: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;speaker-notes&#34;&gt;Speaker Notes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% speaker_note %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Only the speaker can read these notes
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Press &lt;span class=&#34;sb&#34;&gt;`S`&lt;/span&gt; key to view
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  {{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press the &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;aside class=&#34;notes&#34;&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
  
      
      data-background-image=&#34;/media/boards.jpg&#34;
  &gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-slide&#34;&gt;Custom Slide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;background-image&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;/media/boards.jpg&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;background-color&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;#0000FF&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;my-style&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-css-example&#34;&gt;Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create &lt;code&gt;assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code&gt; with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-css&#34; data-lang=&#34;css&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;color&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kc&#34;&gt;navy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/z8wNYzb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Ask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.hugoblox.com/content/slides/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
